Oh my, I just spent a ton of money because of you.
真是的 你让我花了这么多的钱
The condition for forming a two-hundred-year contract with me
跟我缔结两百年契约的条件居然是
is that I have to buy back your remains from the guild?
让我从公会把你的遗骸买回来
Dragons really are a different breed.
龙果然就是不一样啊
I'm sorry, my temporary master.
抱歉 我暂时的主人
I just prefer those with weak bonds not be permitted to do whatever they like with my body.
我实在不喜欢让缘分浅薄之人 随意处置我的肉体
But the beloved pupil of Wandering Balcony, the one who killed me, is a bond that will more than suffice.
但如果是杀死我的放浪栈敷的爱徒 那倒是跟我很有缘分
Don't mind him, my foolish disciple.
你别在意 笨蛋徒弟
There are those like him in the world.
这世上也有这种家伙存在
I formally give you the promise.
那么 我正式在此允许你
The body I'll leave in the mortal plane, you may use as armor to dwell in.
无论是将我留在现世的身体 寄宿于武器上
You may reanimate it into an undead ally,
还是将我作为尸体而利用殆尽
turn it into ingredients for medicine.
或是将我当作药材使用
Or even use it to form a new bond with someone.
又或是让我缔结新的缘分也可以
I have bound you to a dragon's fate.
刚才 我让你和龙缔结了缘分
(Dead Mount, Death Play)
《尸体如山的死亡游戏》
(Episode 20: The Visitors)
(#20 The Visitors-来访者-)
I think novels that have adventurers guilds
我觉得会出现冒险者公会的小说
have a lot in common with shark movies.
与鲨鱼电影非常相似
Don't go saying things that'll piss off the fanbase of either of those.
你不要说这种会让双方的粉丝 感到困惑的话啦
Adventurers guilds are common in otherworldly reincarnations and transfers.
异世界转生或转移的作品中 经常会出现冒险者公会这种背景
GUILD Based on this,
(公会) 许多作品会在此基础上
the authors add some original element
添加各种各样的原创要素
so that each story is ultimately original and unique.
最后创作出不一样的故事
Shark movies are the same.
鲨鱼电影也是这样
They all share the same gimmick, the man-eating shark.
虽然鲨鱼吃人这个背景是一样的
But they'll add a unique twist. Maybe there's a tornado, or ghosts, or demons, or zombies,
但这些作品不是都会加上 龙卷风 幽灵 恶魔 僵尸
or sharks that can swim on sand or through snow. Maybe it's an atomic shark, or a robot, or a mecha,
穿越沙漠 穿越雪原 原子能 机器人 机械装置
or three-headed…
两个脑袋 三个脑袋 中间省略
Or even six-headed.
六个脑袋头等各种各样的要素
And all these different elements make each and every one of them original, see?
来增添原创性吗
Yeah, but aren't period pieces and westerns the same way?
不过 历史剧和西部剧 不也都是这样的吗
Yeah. That's why
是的 也就是说
you could call a period piece and westerns a shark movie.
历史剧和西部剧也可以称作鲨鱼电影
And since they say that all the story archetypes
而且 可以说这世上的故事类型
in the world were covered by Shakespeare.
都被莎士比亚给写完了
SHARKSPEARE
(鲨士比亚)
REPRESENTATIVE WORK: AN EYE FOR AN EYE Maybe Shakespeare was a shark?
(代表作『以尺还尺』) 难道说莎士比亚曾经是鲨鱼吗
Right. So can you get to your point?
好了 你到底想说什么
I'm just trying to say that we should see what's unique
我想说的是我们需要确认美咲小姐
about the kind of "Vampire" Miss Misaki is.
与其他吸血鬼相比有哪些特别之处
Huh? Me?
什么 我吗
Talk about beating around the bush.
你绕圈子也该有个限度吧
I think it's important for us all to know
我认为我们还是先了解一下 美咲小姐跟那些吸血鬼的基础特征
how far from the usual "Vampire" stereotypes Miss Misaki deviates.
有哪里不一样会比较好
Also to keep bad guys from discovering her strengths and weaknesses.
这也是为了不让那些心怀不轨的人 掌握她的强项和短处
Well, you've got a point there.
你说得也对
How about this? Are you okay with sunlight?
对了 你不怕太阳光吗
Yep. Only, it seems a little brighter to me.
嗯 我只是觉得有点刺眼而已
Do you drink blood?
那 你会吸血吗
Huh?
什么
Blood, according to Corpse God,
根据尸神殿所说
is a stimulant for them.
对于它们来说 血就像兴奋剂一样
To convert others into their companions,
为了增加伙伴
they need to give large amounts of their own blood over the course of many years.
它们需要花很多年去 大量传播自己的血
Thus, they rarely feed on blood.
所以它们很少吸血
However, it is possible to improve the breed through magic.
但是 使用魔法就能改良品种了
No, or rather, evolve.
不 也许还能做到进化
Isn't Misaki's transformation into a vampire a typical example?
尸神殿将美咲小姐变成吸血鬼 不就是一个典型的例子吗
Just like a cyborg.
就像改造人一样呢 嘻嘻嘻
LIKE A CYBORG
(像改造人一样呢)
Sorry.
抱歉
I got you involved for my own sake.
把你也卷进我的麻烦之中了
But it was the greatest proof of my trust that I could show you.
这是我所能提供的最大程度的信赖了
I swear on the dragon whose arm that used to be and,
我向曾经拥有这只手臂的龙
and on my master, who allowed me to do this.
以及将其托付给我的师父发誓
I trust you.
我信任你
So please form a pact with me.
所以能否请你与我结为同盟
Lend me your strength.
并助我一臂之力呢
It's unbelievable.
虽然这令人难以置信
Not to mention those tigers.
但包括那只老虎之内
I can't believe you're showing me this.
毕竟你都让我见识到这种东西了
And this shark plushie is?
对了 那只鲨鱼玩偶是什么
Oh. That's the real Polka.
啊 它是真正的波尔卡
-What? -Yeah, yeah.
-什么 -啊
He means Polka is currently possessing
他是说波尔卡正附身在
MECHANICAL ARM AND THE DRAGON'S ARM that stuffed shark toy.
(机械手臂和龙的手臂) 那个鲨鱼玩偶身上
I see.
是吗…
He seems to be enjoying himself in there.
他本人倒是挺乐在其中的
I was pretty dumbfounded myself.
我也非常震惊
I see.
这样啊
And now the spoiled boy says rather than getting back his own body,
所以 他说相比于回到原来的身体 他更希望换成机器人的身体
he'd like his body to change into a robot.
真是个任性的家伙啊
NICE TO MEET YOU Uh, he says nice to meet you, Xiaoyu.
(请多指教) 那个 他要我代他向你问好
Yeah.
嗯
Young Master Polka.
波尔卡少爷
MECHA HAND! DRAGON HAND! OH! Nice to meet you.
(机械手 龙的手 哇 哇) 今后也请你多多关照了
Huh? Is he even more antagonistic with real Polka than with me?
咦 总觉得他对真波尔卡 比对我还要充满敌意
I-In any case,
总 总而言之
I'm happy for your cooperation.
很高兴你愿意帮助我
There is no doubt that we are indeed being targeted.
毋庸置疑的是 我们确实被人给盯上了
When it comes to the organization affiliated with that empire's sigil,
我想尽一切可能地对那个
I want us to prepare ourselves as much as we can.
与帝国徽章有关的组织做些什么
You are…very good at…investigating.
你…很擅长调查
Right, Moth?
对吧 夏虫
This will…benefit you too.
这对你…也有好处
As a moth…who craves that… which transcends…the natural laws.
夏虫…你渴求超乎常理的事物吧
Oh?
哦哦
Their ancestor…is a product… who came from…the other side of the sky.
他们的祖先是… 来自…天空另一侧的…产物
A bug…eating away…at this world.
是侵蚀…这个世界的…虫
The other side of the sky?
天空的另一侧…
Are you saying aliens?
也就是说他们是宇宙人吗
I'm not sure…about that.
这就不知道了
But…it is pretty close to… what you are…looking for.
不过…这是…与你的追求 很相近的…事物之一
Pretty close?
很相近的事物之一
Anything else?
就是说还有其他的吗
You should know…just… as well as we do…Moth.
想必…你自己…也很清楚吧…夏虫
Humph, you're right.
呵呵 说得也是
If my aerial show started it all,
如果说一切都是因我的航空秀 而发生的话
it is all connected.
那这一切一定存在某种关系
Of course, that includes you too.
当然了 你也包括在内
Fire-breathing Bug.
赴火之虫
Oh, you have returned.
你回来了啊
I'll be going back and forth between here and the headquarters for a while.
嗯 我暂时需要往返这里与总部呢
These documents are quite old.
这些资料艇旧的呢
I am digging into the past of Fire-breathing Bug.
我在挖掘赴火之虫的过去
We already knew that Habaki's men and the Fire-breathing Bug were at odds.
毕竟我们已经得知 幅木一派与其对立的事了
Uh-huh.
是吗
Your reactions are as muted as ever.
你还是一如既往的冷淡啊
Fire-breathing Bug has only been on the scene for the past few years.
赴火之虫是在近几年才出现的
Both the police and the media believe this.
我们警察和媒体都是这样想的
Isn't this the truth?
这不是事实吗
THIS WORLD SHOULD BE CONSUMED BY FLAME I found this just this morning.
(要给这个世界以火的…) 我今天早上发现
It seems like they only started using English recently.
他们似乎是最近才开始使用英语的
That means Fire-breathing Bug has been around
实际上在我进入三辑的很久以前开始
since way before I joined Comps-3.
赴火之虫就已经存在了
Okay.
好
Next customer, please.
那么有请下一位编号的客人
Looks like he's pretty popular.
这里好像还挺受欢迎的嘛
It's surprisingly crowded here.
没想到人还挺多的
What's wrong with you? Miss Soara.
你怎么了 索亚拉小姐
Nothing, I don't know why, but…
没有 我自己也不清楚
I just got chills or something deep in my bones.
就是觉得皮肤 不 是我的血有些躁动不安
Oh?
是吗
I feel something's in the air.
我只是觉得气氛有些不对劲…
I'm so jealous.
那真是太让人羡慕了
You must have sensed something.
你一定是感觉到了什么
An unknown power that's not of this world.
与这个世界不相符的未知的力量
After all, the diviner here is the real deal.
毕竟这里的占卜师可是货真价实的
-Check out this video. It happened in this building. -What is that? It's hand! Hand!
-你看 这个视频 是这栋大楼哦 -那是什么 手 手
Is this related to Phantom Solitaire?
这里与怪人雪天鸦有关吗
Although it appears that everyone believes this, I do not.
虽然社会上普遍这么认为 可我却不这么想
Solitaire is always looking for ways to have fun and never acts with a plan.
雪天鸦纯粹只是想找点乐子 作事总是漫无目的
But he likes to surprise the audience.
不过他喜欢让观众大吃一惊
Exactly because of this,
正因如此
it doesn't make sense for him to pull off such an incredible feat without any warning.
他在没有预告的情况下就搞出 这么夸张的动静 实在是不太合理
If it is not a trick,
如果不是戏法的话
was Solitaire attacked by some mystery phenomenon?
雪天鸦难道是 被真正的怪异现象给袭击了吗
Not necessarily.
不 不一定是这样
Meaning?
你的意思是…
He might enjoy playing with those strange hands.
他说不定跟那些诡异的手 玩得挺高兴的呢
That's so overly romantic.
那还真是挺浪漫的呢
Right? It's so romantic.
对吧 真的很浪漫呢
Ticket number 25, please come in.
有请排在第25号的客人
Oh, looks like my number's up.
哎呀 好像到我了
Can I ask you your name?
可以告诉我你的名字吗
I'm Mikoto.
我叫水琴
Saimyouji Mikoto.
西明寺水琴
MIKOTO You can find me on SNS if you search for my name in English.
(MIKOTO) 可用用罗马拼音搜到我的SNS
FORTUNE-TELLING
(占卜)
You two sure hit it off.
你们聊得很开心嘛
Yeah, I guess he and I clicked.
是啊 看来他跟我还挺合得来的
Huh?
是吗
What's wrong?
怎么了
That person just now is a forensic doctor.
刚才那个人是位法医
Oh.
是吗
Please state your name and what you'd like divined.
下一位客人 请说出你的名字 和你想占卜的事情吧
MIKOTO, I'M A FORENSICS SPEALIST IN TOKYO My name is Civil.
(MIKOTO 我在东京从事法医的工作) 嗯 我的名字是塞维利亚
As for what I want divined,
(MIKOTO 我在东京从事法医的工作！) 我想占卜的事情是
I'd like it to be about a fate that spans a hundred years
关于长达一百年的因缘
and new encounters.
与新的邂逅
I 'd like to get Mr. Saimyouji's opinion.
我真想听听西明寺先生的意见
Did he not come today?
他今天没来吗
I didn't see him.
没看到他呢
He must be very busy too, I assume.
他应该也很忙吧
In comparison, he's always here.
但他却很常待在这里呢
He's recently become interested in people who have supernatural abilities.
他最近好像沉迷于灵能力者
Interesting.
真是好搞笑
Huh?
什么
It's the diviner, the young kid who suddenly showed up in town.
就是那个突然出现在新宿的 少年占卜师
Hmm. Young fortune-teller, huh?
是吗 少年占卜…什么
CLOSED
(休息中)
That pen is Prosecutor Hosorogi?
那个自动铅笔是细吕木监察官吗
HEH-HEH. LOOKING FORWARD TO WORKING WITH YOU, KID
(呵呵呵 请多指教 少年)
Phantom Solitaire is likely to be shocked when he finds out about this.
想必怪人雪天鸦知道这事后 也会大吃一惊吧
Huh? No, when I was confronting him before…
呃 我之前跟他对峙的时候
SOLITAIRE SPREADS LIES I'll repay my debt
(满嘴谎话的雪天鸦) 我欠夕律目的人情
to Hozologi another time.
还是下次再还吧
He seemed quite worried.
因为他看起来很担心
I wondered if Prosecutor Hosorogi would be a benefactor of Solitaire.
所以我还想说细吕木监察官 会不会是雪天鸦的恩人
Oh, I see.
这样啊
NO, NO, NO! I HAVE ZERO RECOLLECTION OF THAT GUY!
(不不不 我完全不记得有这回事)
WHAT THE HECK? I'M SCARED! HELP! THE PEN IS WRITING NON-STOP
(怎么回事 好吓人 快救我 满口谎话的笔)
Phantom Solitaire…
怪人雪天鸦
What exactly is his purpose?
他到底有什么样的目的
Is it all right if I call in the next person?
我可以叫下一位了吗
Oh, yes. Please.
啊 嗯 拜托你了
Then I'll get back to work.
那我也回去继续工作了
Sis Sayo requested the Glehnia Root Hot Pot for dinner.
晚饭是小夜姐想吃的切蒲英火锅
Looking forward to it.
我很期待呢
What's this?
怎么回事
What's coming?
是谁来了
Next.
下一位客人来了
Pardon me.
打扰了
Nice to meet you.
初次见面
My name is Civil.
我叫塞维利亚
Thank you for having me.
请多指教
I can't believe it.
真让人难以置信
He is nothing more than a human.
他不过是一个人类而已
I've never seen spirits of the dead so strongly fuse together before.
我从未见过人类身边的死灵 居然能凝聚到这种程度
Even if this person had slaughtering millions on a battlefield,
就算这个人在战场上 杀了一百万个人
it wouldn't be like this.
也不会出现这种情况
These particular spirits of the dead have been maturing for decades and decades…
这些死灵需要花费数年 甚至数十年才能成熟
Besides,
而且
only a very few of these spirits bear ill will.
只有很少一部分的死灵抱有怨恨
The majority feel neither regret nor love but rather…
大多数死灵抱有的情感 既不是留恋也不是爱情
Obsession?
是执着吗
Anything wrong?
怎么了
I'd better not let my anxiety show.
不能让他看出我很慌张
I'll cast the spell of false face on myself
我给自己施加误认相貌的魔法
and paster on a serene smile.
来向他展现平静的表情吧
Looks like you've had a rough life.
看来您度过了一段很坎坷的人生呢
Oh?
哦
Everyone around me says that, but it's been surprisingly dull.
虽然我周围的人都这么说 但其实我的人生还蛮无聊的哦
Hey, what's wrong?
喂 怎么了
Is this normal?
这是在正常占卜吗
I can't make up my mind whether he's a fraud or the real thing.
我无法判断这个人是骗子还是真货
I can tell from the building watchers' cell phones
不过 通过分析监视这栋大楼的人 所携带的手机可以知道
that they monitor and protect the diviner.
他们的任务是监视和保护这位占卜师
Let's pry a little, then.
我稍微探一下他的话吧
That reminds me.
话说回来
That amazing criminal Solitaire came to this building, didn't he?
我听说有个叫雪天鸦的 很厉害的犯罪分子来过这栋大楼
Apparently so.
确实如此
Have you seen him?
你见过他吗
Perhaps I caught a glimpse of him while I was not looking.
嗯 说不定在我没注意到的情况下
Our fates have already crossed.
我们两人的命运就已经产生交集了
Hmm…
唔
I knew it. This computer's functions are severely lacking.
这个电脑的性能果然还是不够啊
I should've asked Granny to put this together.
早知道我就拜托婆婆来制作了
What are you doing?
你在干什么
Just like yesterday…
昨天也是…
I'm hungry, so I'm heading out.
我肚子饿了 先走咯
See you.
掰掰
I never expected you to abandon me and leave.
我没想到你会就这样把我扔下 然后一个人走了
It's just a little mischief.
没什么 不过是个小把戏而已
By the way,
比起这个
now give me a cooler, more celebrity-worthy smile.
你像偶像一样 爽朗地笑一笑吧
Please don't ask for the impossible.
请不要强人所难了
It's alright.
没事的
I believe you can do it.
我相信你可以做到的
Look, more importantly, where's my phone?
先别管这个了 我的手机呢
The police might track down the signal and come here.
警察说不定会循着信号追过来的
It has already…been burned.
已经…烧掉…了
That was expensive.
那只手机很贵耶
You fear…the police more than…you do me?
比起…我…你更害怕…警察…吗
Depending on how things go down.
那要视情况而定了
Even compared to… the products of…Sabaramond?
你害怕…塞巴拉隆多的产物们…吗
Sabaramond?
塞巴拉隆多
What is that?
那是什么
I was just remembering this police officer named Arase.
我只是想起了那个叫荒濑的刑警而已
After all, he could have tortured me.
毕竟他感觉会让我生不如死
Hmph.
哼
So you're not familiar with them?
你真不知道吗
No, I have no idea what you're talking about.
是啊 我完全不知道你在说些什么
Then you and I are comrades!
那么你就是我的同伴了
Huh?
什么
Um.
嗯
COMPLETED, PLEASE CONFIRM
(已经完成了 请您确认)
Let's unearth the secret of Sabaramond together.
我们一起挖出那个 塞巴拉隆多的秘密吧
By joining forces.
就靠我们两个人的力量
So
那么
you want to know about a fate that spans a hundred years?
您的问题是关于长达一百年的因缘
Can I ask you a little more about that?
能请您再详细说明一下吗
Well, let's say
这样啊 比如说
someone committed some unforgivable crime.
假如某个人犯下了不可饶恕的大罪
Do you think those relationships
你会认为除了那个犯下罪过的人之外
should be cursed by the world and face judgment?
他的同伴也应该受到 世界的诅咒与惩罚吗
This is just my personal feeling.
以下只是我个人的想法而已
I'd like to think this world isn't like that.
我希望这里并不是那种世界
I see. Well, usually that's the case.
是吗 一般都会这么想吧
There are, however, some troublesome people
可是我和我的伙伴们
who still hate my friends and me for things
却因为一百年前的事 而遭到他人的怨恨
that happened a hundred years ago.
现在正被一群麻烦的家伙所困扰
That's terrible.
那还真是辛苦您了
If there's anything I can do,
如果有我能帮到的地方
allow me to offer whatever help I am able.
请您尽管开口
"Terrible"?
辛苦…吗
It's the other way around, Mr. Diviner.
正好相反呢 占卜师先生
I want to encounter those unreasonable guys as soon as possible.
我倒是想早点碰到 那群不讲理的家伙呢
Huh?
什么
Think about it.
你觉得我说得对不对
The reason we're kicked down,
被打的理由
the reason we're despised,
被恨的理由
the reason we're hated,
被讨厌的理由
or the reason why we've earned their malice…
或者是让人起了杀心的理由
The more unreasonable, the better.
通常都是越不合理越好
What do you mean?
这是什么意思
I don't owe those people anything, right?
我并不欠那些人什么 对吧
Then, I can crush insects with a clear conscience.
那么 我就能以一种纯粹的心情 来辗死那些虫子了
And there will be no guilt at all.
而且并不会有任何的愧疚
Isn't that…
这…
doing the same thing as your adversary?
到头来您的所作所为 与对方又有什么区别呢
Yes, so it's about the order of operations.
没错 所以这就是先后顺序的问题了
CRIME If my friend committed the wrong-doing first
(罪人) 如果一开始是我的同伴犯下罪过
and the adversary sought revenge against just that friend,
并遭到他人复仇的话
they would have every right to do so.
那确实是对方有理
But if the adversary hates me
可如果我 我的同伴们
for the sole reason that I am related to the wrongdoer,
只因为是犯罪者的同伴 而遭到他人怨恨的话
that starts a whole new attack.
由此又会展开新的攻击
If so, should I not, in turn, be allowed
那么如果我们同样 向对方的同伴动手的话
to make a move against my adversary's friends?
是不是就可以被原谅呢
Well, it's not the same.
这…不一样
Once I can pass undetected by the eyes of the law,
只要能钻过法律的漏洞
I can pursue any destruction by insult to maximum effect.
就可以尽情地享受破坏与凌辱
Don't you think that would feel wonderful?
你不觉得这是非常痛快的事情吗
He's different from those kids.
这家伙和那些孩子们不一样
Those children
他和那时
were killed for no reason when they were with me back then.
只因为跟我在一起
He's not like them.
就毫不合理地被杀害的孩子们不一样
Allow me to ask you one thing.
我有一个问题想问您
Do you mean
您刚才所说的话
everything you just said?
都是发自内心的吗
What do you think?
是不是呢
Maybe you should try divining it to see?
不然你来占卜一下看看
Very well. Let's do that.
好 那我就这么做吧
What is it? Lulu.
你怎么了 露露
Huh? I don't want to do the fortune telling anymore.
咦 总觉得突然没那个心情了
Hmm? Huh?
咦 奇怪
-I'm sorry, I'm going to have to cancel for today. -I have to get home.
-抱 抱歉 我今天就不占卜了 -我得回去了
Huh? Huh?
咦 咦
He hasn't figured out what I'm doing.
看来他并没有察觉到我的动作
At least he doesn't have the Evil Eye to see ghosts and the dead.
至少他并没有 能够看见死灵和灵魂的亚眼
In that case,
那么接下来
I'll give his senses a shake
我就直接接触他的灵魂
and touch his soul directly.
使他的精神产生动摇吧
Calm your heart and entrust it
请您让您的心灵接受空间的动摇吧
to the fluctuations of this space.
让内心冷静下来
These spirits
这些死灵们
are trying to protect?
在试图防御吗
It's the first time I've felt this.
我第一次体会到这种感觉
The magic in my body just burst.
魔力在身体里被弹开了
What just happened to me?
我被做了什么
Could it be that
难道
this boy is a visitor from another world?
这个少年是来自异世界的访问者吗
What's with this dense magic power?
这魔力的密度是怎么回事
It's on par with the imperial court sorcerers?
居然有帝国宫廷魔法师的程度
Is he really even a human of this world?
他真的是这个世界的人类吗
But I have investigated Polka Shinoyama.
可是 我调查过四乃山波尔卡
He is undoubtedly a human born in this world.
他毫无疑问是诞生于这个世界的人类
so is he a stand-in?
难道他是替身吗
Perhaps he's from the other side of sky?
还是说他来自天空彼端的…
Or maybe there could be someone manipulating him?
不 说不定是有人在背后操控他
Interesting.
真是有趣
What an incredible feeling.
这感觉真是不可思议啊
Just now, did you do something to me?
你刚刚是不是对我做了什么
Well. It could have been that dormant fate
这样啊 那或许是您内心 沉睡着的命运
within you awakening.
已经苏醒过来了
Please allow me to search your soul a little deeper.
请让我再深入探索一下您的灵魂
I need to figure out a safe way to get through this.
我还是想办法平安度过这个局面为好
But it was so close.
可是就差一点了
Hmm…
哦
I can't wait to see what comes out of it.
会发生什么事呢 我好期待哦
I too am eager to know
我也想知道
what's lurking inside me.
我的心里到底潜藏着什么
You might be happier
真正的自己究竟是什么样的
not knowing about your true self.
也许还是不知道为好
Lord Civil!
塞维利亚大人
I received a guidance!
引导出现了
This place is dangerous!
这里很危险
Who is this young girl?
这个小孩是谁
A very high-ranked stone elf…
是相当高级别的石精灵…
BYANDY EMPIRE CHANCELLOR, LEUF VELLIZE Is this the child?
(巴亚蒂帝国宰相 露芙维尔莱兹) 就是这个孩子吗
To be sold while still so young.
这么小就被卖了
His family should naturally be able to see elves.
这家伙的种族本来应该是 可以看见精灵的
But apparently, the Evil Eye was too much for them.
但是即便如此 他好像也无法处理亚眼
You're only able to hear the voices of elves, right?
我记得你只能听见精灵的声音 对吧
Honorable Chancellor?
宰相阁下
The Evil Eye is simultaneously both the eyes and the ears.
亚眼既是眼睛也是耳朵
It must be much harder for you than it is for us, who have only one of them.
比起只有其中之一的我们 想必你要辛苦多了吧
But you should live on in strength.
但是只要努力活下来就行了
For elf and spirits of the dead alike
不管是精灵还是死灵
are constant companions at our side.
都是经常陪伴在我们身边的邻居
So that's it.
原来如此
We were just getting to the good part. You can't take care of it for me?
我现在正进行得如火如荼呢 你就不能想个办法吗
But guidance…
可是 引导…
Quit it, boss. Lulu's ears are never wrong.
你放弃吧 老大 露露的耳朵 是不容置疑的
The color of that woman's soul…
那个女人的灵魂的颜色…
The bugs might be setting fire to this place.
而且那些虫子说不定 正准备把这里烧得一干二净啊
Bugs? Is she referring to Fire-breathing Bug?
虫子 他们与赴火之虫有什么关系
Oh, rather than that…
不 比起这个
If it were just one, I'd be able to call it a coincidence.
如果只有一个人或许还可以说是偶然
But there are three of them, deeply clad in the colors of my former world.
可是现在却有三个人 将我所在的世界染上了厚重的颜色
Then it is inevitable.
那么这就是必然了
These three have come to see me.
这些孩子是来找我的
They are the vanguards from the other world.
他们是异世界的先锋
Even though I had my spirits of the dead lead out all the customers…
虽说客人已经 在死灵的诱导下离开了…
What to do?
怎么办
Should I keep them here?
我要留住他们吗
Come on, hurry up and leave.
好了 我们赶快走吧
Sorry, Mr. Diviner.
抱歉 占卜师先生
I will come see you again.
我下次再来见你
Next time,
下次
it'll be as a friend.
我会作为你的朋友而来
Miss Soara!
索亚拉小姐
It's you, isn't it?
就是你吧
You're the assailant who's been showing up all over the place lately.
最近那个蠢蠢欲动的袭击者
(Episode 21: The Spirit)
(#21 The Spirit-精灵-)